<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FREE STORIES</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="word1">Nothing can stop you, if you have strong determination.</string>
    <string name="word2">Successes comes to those who have ideas and spirit to stand again.</string>
    <string name="word3">Its better to think twice before you say and do anything.</string>
    <string name="word4"> In life, you get what you give. Don’t try and cheat others.</string>

    <string name="motive_stroy1"> 
            A gentleman was walking through an elephant camp, and he spotted that the elephants weren’t being kept in
            cages or held by the use of chains.\n\n All that was holding them back from escaping the camp, was a small piece of rope tied
            to one of their legs. As the man gazed upon the elephants, he was completely confused as to why the elephants didn’t just use
            their strength to break the rope and escape the camp. They could easily have done so, but instead, they didn’t try to at all.
            Curious and wanting to know the answer, he asked a trainer nearby why the elephants were just standing there and never tried
            to escape. \n\n
            The trainer replied; “when they are very young and much smaller we use the same size rope to tie them and, at that
            age, it’s enough to hold them. As they grow up, they are conditioned to believe they cannot break away.
            They believe the rope can still hold them, so they never try to break free.”
            The only reason that the elephants weren’t breaking free and escaping from the camp was that over time they adopted the
            belief that it just wasn’t possible.\n\n
            Moral of the story:\n
            No matter how much the world tries to hold you back, always continue with the belief that what you want to achieve is possible.
            Believing you can become successful is the most important step in actually achieving it.</string>

    <string name="motive_story2">
            In a small Italian town, hundreds of years ago, a small business owner owed a large sum of money
            to a loan-shark. The loan-shark was a very old, unattractive looking guy that just so happened to fancy the business
            owner’s daughter. He decided to offer the businessman a deal that would completely wipe out the debt he owed him.
            However, the catch was that we would only wipe out the debt if he could marry the businessman’s daughter.\n\n
            Needless to say, this proposal was met with a look of disgust.
            The loan-shark said that he would place two pebbles into a bag, one white and one black.
            The daughter would then have to reach into the bag and pick out a pebble. If it was black, the debt would be wiped,
            but the loan-shark would then marry her.\n\n
            If it was white, the debt would also be wiped, but the daughter wouldn’t have to marry the loan-shark.
            Standing on a pebble-strewn path in the businessman’s garden, the loan-shark bent over and picked up two pebbles.
            Whilst he was picking them up, the daughter noticed that he’d picked up two black pebbles and placed them both into the bag.
            He then asked the daughter to reach into the bag and pick one.\n\n
            The daughter naturally had three choices as to what she could have done: Refuse to pick a pebble from the bag.
            Take both pebbles out of the bag and expose the loan-shark for cheating.
            Pick a pebble from the bag fully well knowing it was black and sacrifice herself for her father’s freedom.
            She drew out a pebble from the bag, and before looking at it ‘accidentally’ dropped it into the midst of the other pebbles.\n\n
            She said to the loan-shark; “Oh, how clumsy of me. Never mind, if you look into the bag for the one that is left,
            you will be able to tell which pebble I picked.”
            The pebble left in the bag is obviously black, and seeing as the loan-shark didn’t want to be exposed, he had to play
            along as if the pebble the daughter dropped was white, and clear her father’s debt.\n\n
            Moral of the story:\n
            It’s always possible to overcome a tough situation throughout of the box thinking, and not give in to the only
            options you think you have to pick from.</string>

    <string name="motive_story3">
            As a group of frogs was traveling through the woods, two of them fell into a deep pit.\n\n
            When the other frogs crowded around the pit and saw how deep it was, they told the two frogs that there was no hope
            left for them. However, the two frogs decided to ignore what the others were saying and they proceeded to try and jump
            out of the pit. Despite their efforts, the group of frogs at the top of the pit were still saying that they should just give up.
            That they would never make it out.\n\n
            Eventually, one of the frogs took heed to what the others were saying and he gave up, falling down to his death.
            The other frog continued to jump as hard as he could. Again, the crowd of frogs yelled at him to stop the pain and just die.
            He jumped even harder and finally made it out. When he got out, the other frogs said, “Did you not hear us?”
            The frog explained to them that he was deaf. He thought they were encouraging him the entire time.\n\n
            Moral of the story: \n
            People’s words can have a big effect on other’s lives. Think about what you say before it comes out of your mouth.
            It might just be the difference between life and death.</string>

    <string name="motive_story4">
            There was a farmer who sold a pound of butter to a baker. One day the baker decided to weigh the butter to see
            if he was getting the right amount, which he wasn’t. Angry about this, he took the farmer to court.\n\n
            The judge asked the farmer if he was using any measure to weight the butter. The farmer replied, “Honor, I am primitive.
            I don’t have a proper measure, but I do have a scale.”
            The judge asked, “Then how do you weigh the butter?” \n\n
            The farmer replied;\n
            “Your Honor, long before the baker started buying butter from me, I have been buying a pound loaf of bread from him.
            Every day when the baker brings the bread, I put it on the scale and give him the same weight in butter.
            If anyone is to be blamed, it is the baker.” \n\n
            Moral of the story: \n
            In life, you get what you give. Don’t try and cheat others.</string>


</resources>